http://www.indianweddingsaree.com/static/privacy-policy.aspx

Password
Forgot Password?
New User? Sign Up
Email
Password
EXCITING OFFERS! - Minimum 30% to Maximum 50% off.
Free shipping on orders above US$ 79.00
24x7 Support:
Your cart (0
Items)
VIEW CART & CHECKOUT
U.S. Dollar (US$)
Canadian Dollar (CA$)
Pound Sterling (£)
Euro (€)
Australian Dollar (AU$)
Mauritian Rupee (MUR)
Swedish Krona (SEK)
Hong Kong Dollar (HKD)
Japanese Yen (JPY)
Malaysian Ringgit (MYR)
Norwegian Krone (NOK)
New Zealand Dollar (NZD)
Philippine Peso (PHP)
Singapore Dollar (SGD)
Swiss Franc (CHF)
Taiwan New Dollar (TWD)
Thai Baht (THB)
Polish Zloty (PLN)
Fijian Dollar (FJD)
Trinidadian Dollar (TTD)
Indian Rupee (Rs.)
Saree OccasionBollywoodBridalCasualDesignerFestiveParty WearReceptionTraditionalWeddingAll Occasions...StyleBengaliClassicHalf & HalfDrapedPaithaniPattuRajasthaniRuffleAll Style...SouthColorBeige and BrownBlack and GreyBlueGoldOrangePink and MajentaPurple and VioletRed and MaroonWhite and Off WhiteAll Color...WorkBandhejBorderCut DanaLacePatchPrintedReshamStoneThreadAll Work...FabricArt SilkBanarasi SilkCottonFaux ChiffonFaux GeorgetteHandloomKanjeevaram SilkNetSilkAll Fabric...MoreBest SellersNew ArrivalsReady to ShipReadymade SareeBlouseAll Sarees...Salwar OccasionBollywoodBridalCasualDesignerFestiveEngagementMehendi SangeetParty WearReceptionWeddingAll Occasions...StyleAbayaAnarkaliAsymmetricalPakistaniChuridarPalazzoPatialaShararaSlitsStraightAll Style...ColorBeige and BrownBlack and GreyBlueGoldOrangePink and MajentaPurple and VioletRed and MaroonWhite and Off WhiteAll Color...WorkEmbroideredLacePatchPrintedReshamSequenceStoneThreadZariAll Work...FabricArt SilkBanarasi SilkChanderi SilkCottonFaux GeorgetteGeorgetteNetRayonSilkAll Fabric...MoreBest SellersNew ArrivalsDupattaReady to ShipReadymadeSemi stitchedDress materialGownAll Salwar Kameez...Lehenga OccasionBollywoodBridalDesignerEngagementFestiveMehendi SangeetParty WearTraditionalWeddingAll Occasions...StyleA LineFish CutLehnga Style SareesLong Lehenga CholiAll Style...Rajputi PoshakColorBeige and BrownBlack and GreyBlueGreenOrangePink and MajentaPurple and VioletRed and MaroonWhite and Off WhiteAll Color...WorkBorderCut DanaEmbroideredPatchReshamSequenceStoneThreadZariAll Work...FabricArt SilkBanarasi SilkGeorgetteJacquardNetSatin SilkSilkTaffeta SilkVelvetAll Fabric...MoreBest SellersNew ArrivalsReady to ShipReady To Ship Lehenga SareesRajputi PoshakAll Lehengas...New Arrivals Shop CollectionKurta PyjamaKurtis (Tunics)LehengaSalwar KameezSareesSherwaniIndo Western TunicsAnarkaliAbayaBollywoodCasualCotton DesignerParty WearPrintedTunics Best SellersAll Tunics...Tunics with BottomCasualDesignerFestiveParty WearPalazzoStraightWeddingAll Tunics with Bottom...BottomsChuridarJeggingsLeggingsPalazzoPatialaShortsSkirtMoreDressDupattaGownKaftanAbayaTops & ShirtsPlus Plus Size CollectionSalwar KameezTunicsGownKurta PyjamaMen SherwaniDhoti SherwaniWedding SherwaniSuits2 Piece Suit (with shirt)2 Piece Suit (without shirt)3 Piece Suit (with shirt)Jodhpuri SuitTuxedoKurtaDhoti KurtaDhoti Kurta with JacketKurta OnlyKurta Pajama with JacketKurta PyjamaPathaniIndo WesternBlazerIndo WesternNehru JacketMoreCufflinksGroom NecklaceMojariSafaStoleKids GirlsGownLehengaSalwar KameezSareeBoysDhoti KurtaIndo WesternKurta PyjamaSherwaniJewelry Shop CollectionAnkletsArmletBanglesBraceletsChainChallaEarringsMask ChainNecklacesPendantsRingsWeddingHaath PaanMaang TikkaMangalsutraNose RingBridal JewelryPassaWaist ChainAccessories Shop CollectionBindiCloth MaskHandbags, Slings & ClutchesPotliTattoosWomen Shoes
Sale
Currency
Login
Wishlist
Privacy Policy
Home / Privacy Policy
We make every effort to preserve user privacy. If you feel that this company is disclosing user privacy, you should first contact Our Customer Support Manager at: privacy@indianweddingsaree.com; Tel: 91 141
4028090; Fax : 91 141 6608080
Information Collection and use
In order to purchase from www.IndianWeddingSaree.com, a user have to provide some basic required information to process orders include: name, email address, street address, and phone number. This information is essential for customer's orders to be processed and delivered. It is optional for users to give information such as: gender, product interests, etc. This information is used by Indian Wedding Saree to better serve and protects its valued customers.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Please note that the access logs collected for www.IndianWeddingSaree.com and www.IndianWeddingSaree.com contain more information than just IP addresses. They also let us know what operating system/Internet browser you use and what pages on our site you have viewed. As with your IP address, this information is not linked to personally identifiable information and is used in aggregate to ensure the functionality of the site for our visitors.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Indian Wedding Saree is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Tell-A-Friend
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Indian Wedding Saree will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Indian Wedding Saree uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and the information is not stored thereafter.
Supplementation of Information
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. We use this information to ensure that the data we have is as up-to-date as possible.
Special Offers
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications when registering.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the My Account page or by emailing our Customer Support department (support@indianweddingsaree.com).
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our registration form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.
users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at privacy@indianweddingsaree.com.
users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email. users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or your dealings with Indian Wedding Saree (www.indianweddingsaree.com), you can contact:
CRM Manager - Customer Relationship Management
Readiprint Fashions
Lane Number 4, #43B, Kartarpura Ind. Area
Bais Godam,
Jaipur - 302006
Rajasthan, India
Phone :+91 86969 55555
Fax: +91 141 6608080 (24 Hours)
email : helpdesk@indianweddingsaree.com
Become a preferred subscriber and get special offers.
© 2020 READIPRINT FASHIONS, JAIPUR, INDIA | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
[{{getSelectedCount(cat,item.field)}}]
{{cat.name}}
[{{cat.count}}]
{{currency}} {{(item.discounted_price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
Ready To Ship
Out Of Stock
{{item.title | truncate(20)}}
{{currency}} {{(item.price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
{{currency}} {{(item.discounted_price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
More Details
Ready To Ship
Out Of Stock
{{currency}} {{(item.price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
{{currency}} {{(item.discounted_price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
More Details
Ready To Ship
Out Of Stock
{{currency}} {{(item.price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
{{currency}} {{(item.discounted_price*currencyMultiplier).toFixed(2)}}
Results Ends Here
Filter
Clear
{{f.title}}
({{giveFilterSelected(f.field)}})
